Museums of Washington and Lee University - Record Group 34 WLU.RG.0034
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
- James Whitehead Papers, 1975-1992; WLU-RG-34; Whitehead, James Walter, Sr.; 8 Linear Feet
  - Box 5: George Washington through Louise Herreshoff (Box 5)
    - Herreshoff and Chinese Export Porcelain (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - Herreshoff Paintings (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - Art Matters (Miscellaneous) (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Herreshoff Catalogues Sold (through Bob Keefes' office) (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - Ruder and Finn and Louise Herreshoff Publicity and Promotion (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - Louise Herreshoff Exhibit, Lexington, Virginia (Box 5, Folder 260)
  - Box 6: Herreshoff and Reeves Collection (Box 6)
    - Herreshoff Paintings, Whitehead, James Walter, Sr. (Box 6, Folder 261)
      Herreshoff, Louise
    - Tulsa, Oklahoma - Herreshoff Paintings (Norman C. Smith) (Box 6, Folder 262)
    - Herreshoff Paintings Related (Box 6, Folder 263)
    - Louise Herreshoff Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 264)
    - Louise Herreshoff Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 265)
    - Louise Herreshoff Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 266)
    - Corcoran Gallery (Louise Herreshoff Opening), 1976-10 (Box 6, Folder 267)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art, D.C. (Herreshoff Paintings and Reviews) (Box 6, Folder 268)
    - Louise Herreshoff Publicity (Box 6, Folder 269)
    - Louise Herreshoff Publicity (Box 6, Folder 270)
    - Herreshoff Paintings (Box 6, Folder 271)
    - Louise Herreshoff Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 272)
    - Louise Herreshoff Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 273)
    - William H. Gertz (Box 6, Folder 274)
    - Blaffer Museum - University of Houston (Box 6, Folder 275)
    - Brandywine River Museum (Box 6, Folder 276)
    - Brandywine River Museum (Box 6, Folder 277)
    - Washington D.C. Antiques Show (Box 6, Folder 278)
    - Washington D.C. Antiques Show (Box 6, Folder 279)
  - Box 7: Travel Exhibitions for Herreshoff and Misc. Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Exhibition Itinerary, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - Chinese Export Porcelain Catalogue (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - The Original Art Report - Frank Salantrie (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - Austin, Texas (University of Texas) (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - Belle Grove Incorporated (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - Birmingham Museum of Art (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - Campbell Museum (Camden, New Jersey) (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - Charleston, West Virginia - Sunrise Art Gallery (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - Charlotte, North Carolina - Mint Antique Show (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - Charlottesville, Virginia (Heritage Antiques Show - Bruce Hobbs, Chairman) (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - Chattanooga, Tennessee - Hunter Museum of Art (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - Dallas Museum of Fine Arts (Box 7, Folder 291)
    - Huntsville Museum of Art - Huntsville, Alabama (Box 7, Folder 292)
    - Jacksonville Antiques Show, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 293)
    - Cummer Gallery of Art - Jacksonville, FL (Box 7, Folder 294)
    - London Show (Box 7, Folder 295)
    - London - Show of Reeves Collections (Box 7, Folder 296)
    - London Antiques Show, 1985-05 (Box 7, Folder 297)
    - Lynchburg Historical Foundation - 3rd Annual Antiques Show and Sale (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - Louisville, Kentuckjy (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - Mississippi Show (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - Montgomery Museum of Fine Arts (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - Pennsbury Manor, Spring Seminar, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 302)
    - Nashville, Tennesse - Cheekwood Mirror (Box 7, Folder 303)
    - Nashville, Tennessee - Cheekwood Museum (Box 7, Folder 304)
    - Contemporary Arts Center - New Orleans, Louisiana (Box 7, Folder 305)
    - Norfolk Show - Chrysler Museum (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - Norfolk Show - Chrysler Museum (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - Orlando, Florida - Loch Have Art Center (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - Parkersburg, West Virginia - Parkersburg Art Center (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - Phoenix Art Museum, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - John Brown House - Providence, Rhode Island (Box 7, Folder 311)
  - Box 8: Misc. (Box 8)
    - Richmond Antiques Show, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 312)
    - Richmond Antiques Show, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 313)
    - Richmond, Virginia (Box 8, Folder 314)
    - First National Exchange Bank (Roanoke - Display of Porcelain Pieces) (Box 8, Folder 315)
    - Roswell Museum and Arts Center (Box 8, Folder 316)
    - M.H. DeYoung Museum - San Francisco, California (Box 8, Folder 317)
    - Shreveport, Louisiana - Norton Art Gallery (Box 8, Folder 318)
    - Tampa Museum - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1989-01 (Box 8, Folder 319)
    - Smithsonian Institute (Box 8, Folder 320)
    - Waynesboro, Virginia - Fall Foliage Festival, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 321)
    - Thorns Craven (Box 8, Folder 322)